In this video, we will talk about
job vacancies of ICICI Lombard. Here you are
hiring for the post of Unit
Sales Manager. We will talk about the job vacancies in
detail. You can read here in detail about the job vacancies for the South location, for
Andhra Pradesh, for Telangana.
How to apply,
we will cover everything in this video. So friend, if we talk about the
responsibilities of the job, then the rules
and responsibilities here are
Acquiring new health agents and advisors
on a regular basis, Licensing and
tracking activation of the same, regularly
Handling the health related products,
Building relationships with health agents,
Regular visits on field for sales of health
policies and agents and individuals, right, that
means whoever you are here as
a unit sales manager, then whoever will
work under you, whoever will be your
agent, your agent will be
individual, you will maintain those ties
so that whatever your product
sells out to you, regularly, right, the
next point is your coordinating.  With
other departments like Underwriting, Claims
and Operations to meet Agents, Lead Providers,
Intermediaries on regular basis and
maintaining records in a planned manner. The simple
thing is that you will be a Unit Sales
Manager and whoever is providing the leads and from wherever the
leads are coming,
you have to maintain a healthy relationship with whoever is working between you so that
your work gets done timely. So let's
talk about Preferred Candidate Profile:
At least six months of field sales
experience If you have sales experience in any company for at
least six months,
you are eligible here
Graduation is mandatory Candidate holding
Diploma and part time degree certificate
will not fit in criteria If you have done part time
degree or diploma then
you are not eligible here If you are a
graduate from any stream then you can
apply Candidate with Operation
background will not be fit for this job
profile Even if you have an Operation background
then you will not fit here  You will get it
You should have knowledge of sales You should have sales
experience Need to work on
100% on field For sales of health policies,
you may have to work 100% in the field here
Right on health policies, if we talk about
perks and benefits then there is five days working
Saturday and Sunday will be off Travelling
petrol reimbursement is available for you and
mediclaim and life insurance
Candidate will be on the payroll of the
organization Whichever ICSE
Lombard you are, you will be totally on their payroll
Any candidate who is interested can
share their resume on Ruchita Sudh@t IILderd If you are an
Eicher, you can contact them on this number
Hiring is going on for
Telangana location and also you can read locations
and you can read Andhra Pradesh and other
locations as well Any
candidate who is interested can apply for this, there is a
process to apply, you have to share your resume
And you have to call, the number is in front, thank you
for watching this video.